<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<activity acttype="true_false" version="1.1" client="McGraw-Hill" oae-label="ACTIVITY TYPE: TRUE/FALSE">

	<!-- This activity presents the student with a series of up to 10 True/False questions on a sinlge page. -->

	<title oae-label="Title">
		<![CDATA[Activity 1]]>
	</title>
	<instructions oae-label="Instructions" oae-type="textarea" oae-rows="3">
		<![CDATA[Read the article. Mark each statement <u>True</u> or <u>False</u>, according to the article.]]>
	</instructions>
	<graphic oae-label="graphic file name (optional). Please include the file extension (.jpg or .png)" oae-type="textarea" oae-rows="1">
		<![CDATA[]]>
	</graphic>
	<audio oae-label="audio file name (optional). Please include the file extension (.mp3)" oae-type="textarea" oae-rows="1">
		<![CDATA[]]>
	</audio>
	<reader oae-label="Reading text (optional)." oae-type="textarea" oae-rows="10">
		<![CDATA[<b>Language and Culture in Today’s Global Culture</b> 

   Language is a powerful reflection of culture. The Japanese language, perhaps more than any other language, has historically and traditionally marked comparative status between speaker and listener. Verb endings, adjectives, and even whole words change in relation to the identity, social standing, gender, and age of the speakers. However, as the culture of the world rapidly becomes less diverse (or more homogeneous) through globalization of business, it seems clear that some of the linguistic aspects of Japanese cultural behavior will change. 

   One characteristic of Japanese culture can be seen in the way people address each other. In recent years, some Japanese people have become aware of the impact traditional forms of address can have on communication within a corporate culture. Elpida Memory, a leading manufacturer of Dynamic Random Access Memory (DRAM) integrated circuits, has recently changed the etiquette of interpersonal communication in their offices.  Corporate management there believed that the traditional forms of address were hindering open communication and were interfering with good communication among employees. In the past, Elpida employees always used to address each other with titles and last names, which is characteristic of traditional corporate culture. However, the company has found that when employees stopped using titles and last names and instead began to address each other with the less formal suffix <i>–san</i> after names, the culture of the corporation became more open and less competitive. 

   The change at Elpida is not unique. For the last decade, other linguistic features of traditional Japanese culture have been diminishing in use. One example is the use of <i>keigo</i>, or honorific language. <i>Keigo</i> is a means of address that emphasizes the importance and social standing of the person addressed in comparison to the humble status of the person speaking. Though <i>keigo</i> was traditionally used in schools, most schools no longer expect children to use it to address their teachers. 

   It’s possible that the changes in Japanese language and forms of address would not be changing if there were no globalization. It is clear, though, that as Japanese and non-Japanese people interact in the course of doing business, the characteristics of traditional Japanese linguistic behavior are becoming less prevalent.]]>
	</reader>
	<spacer oae-type="spacer">
</spacer>

	<!-- Use the following options to modify how the activity will be displayed. Use the first to modify the size of the font, and the following two to indicate what the headers of the "True" and "False" columns should display. -->

	<fontsize oae-label="Resize Font?" oae-type="select" value="0 (Normal)" opt1="-3" opt2="-2" opt3="-1" opt4="0 (Normal)" opt5="+1" opt6="+2" opt7="+3">
</fontsize>
	<headertrue oae-label="True column header">
		<![CDATA[True]]>
	</headertrue>
	<headerfalse oae-label="False column header">
		<![CDATA[False]]>
	</headerfalse>

	<!-- Enter up to 10 statements and indicate if they are true or false; leave "not used" if that item will not be used. -->

	<pairs oae-label="Statement Pairs:">
		<pair oae-label="Pair 1">
			<question oae-label="Statement">
				<![CDATA[People of different status have always spoken Japanese in the same way.]]>
			</question>
			<answer oae-label="Answer" oae-type="select" value="False" opt1="True" opt2="False" opt3="not used">
</answer>
			<feedback oae-label="Feedback">
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</feedback>
		</pair>
		<pair oae-label="Pair 2">
			<question oae-label="Statement">
				<![CDATA[Some of the features of Japanese that can mark status are verb endings and adjectives.]]>
			</question>
			<answer oae-label="Answer" oae-type="select" value="True" opt1="True" opt2="False" opt3="not used">
</answer>
			<feedback oae-label="Feedback">
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</feedback>
		</pair>
		<pair oae-label="Pair 3">
			<question oae-label="Statement">
				<![CDATA[Homogeneous means “more diverse.”]]>
			</question>
			<answer oae-label="Answer" oae-type="select" value="False" opt1="True" opt2="False" opt3="not used">
</answer>
			<feedback oae-label="Feedback">
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</feedback>
		</pair>
		<pair oae-label="Pair 4">
			<question oae-label="Statement">
				<![CDATA[Globalization will contribute to Japanese cultural change.]]>
			</question>
			<answer oae-label="Answer" oae-type="select" value="True" opt1="True" opt2="False" opt3="not used">
</answer>
			<feedback oae-label="Feedback">
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</feedback>
		</pair>
		<pair oae-label="Pair 5">
			<question oae-label="Statement">
				<![CDATA[Forms of address are a reflection of culture.]]>
			</question>
			<answer oae-label="Answer" oae-type="select" value="True" opt1="True" opt2="False" opt3="not used">
</answer>
			<feedback oae-label="Feedback">
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</feedback>
		</pair>
		<pair oae-label="Pair 6">
			<question oae-label="Statement">
				<![CDATA[Japanese culture has had a traditional way for people to address each other.]]>
			</question>
			<answer oae-label="Answer" oae-type="select" value="True" opt1="True" opt2="False" opt3="not used">
</answer>
			<feedback oae-label="Feedback">
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</feedback>
		</pair>
		<pair oae-label="Pair 7">
			<question oae-label="Statement">
				<![CDATA[Elpida Memory is interested in having a corporate culture with more open communication.]]>
			</question>
			<answer oae-label="Answer" oae-type="select" value="True" opt1="True" opt2="False" opt3="not used">
</answer>
			<feedback oae-label="Feedback">
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</feedback>
		</pair>
		<pair oae-label="Pair 8">
			<question oae-label="Statement">
				<![CDATA[Elpida has asked employees to use honorifics.]]>
			</question>
			<answer oae-label="Answer" oae-type="select" value="False" opt1="True" opt2="False" opt3="not used">
</answer>
			<feedback oae-label="Feedback">
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</feedback>
		</pair>
		<pair oae-label="Pair 9">
			<question oae-label="Statement">
				<![CDATA[Elpida employees used the <i>–san</i> suffix with all other employees in the past.]]>
			</question>
			<answer oae-label="Answer" oae-type="select" value="False" opt1="True" opt2="False" opt3="not used">
</answer>
			<feedback oae-label="Feedback">
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</feedback>
		</pair>
		<pair oae-label="Pair 10">
			<question oae-label="Statement">
				<![CDATA[Most school children no longer use <i>keigo</i> at school.]]>
			</question>
			<answer oae-label="Answer" oae-type="select" value="True" opt1="True" opt2="False" opt3="not used">
</answer>
			<feedback oae-label="Feedback">
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</feedback>
		</pair>
	</pairs>
</activity>
